





Summary

Jump to Section

Front-end Developer with over 6+ years of experience in creating a responsive and mobile-first web application. Familiar in working with front-end frameworks like Angular, React and integrating it with the various back-end environments like Node JS. Net. RoR. JSP.

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Work Experience

MSys Tech India Pvt. Ltd as Technical Lead Sep 2018 to Till Date

Frontend Developer With experience in React (3+ Years), Angular (3+ Years), Javascript (6+ Years), HTML (6+ Years), CSS (6+ Years)

- Cybage as Software Engineer Sep 2017 to Sep 2018
- Sri Granth Software Pvt. Ltd as UI Developer Nov 2016 to Sep 2017
- Axlerate India Private Limited as UI Developer Feb 2014 to Nov 2016
 Javascript, HTML, CSS

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Sri Ramanujar Engineering College - Anna University in 2013

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
React JS, Angular 2/4/6/8, JavaScript	
Radius iOijans HTMI 5 CSS3	

1

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

Neuux, jouery, rinveo, 0000.	
Figma, Axure, Invision	
GIMP, Photoshop, Illustrator	
Rally, Jira, Clubhouse	
MYSQL, ORACLE	
AWS, IIS, Apache	
SQL Certified Expert, PL/SQL	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Tamil				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General
Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.